let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "What was the fastest growing web browser in 2020?",
        answer: "A. Microsoft Edge",
        options: [
            "A. Microsoft Edge",
            "B. Firefox",
            "C. DuckDuckGo",
            "D. Internet Explorer",

        ]
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "Which University offered the first-ever academic programme in Computer Science?",
        answer: "D. Cambridge University",
        options: [
            "A. Harvard University",
            "B. MIT",
            "C. University of Glasgow",
            "D. Cambridge University",
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "How much did Steve Jobs first computer go for at auction?",
        answer: "B. $500,000",
        options: [
            "A. $1.2 million",
            "B. $500,000",
            "C. $223,000",
            "D. $3.4 million"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "Which model of computer is the best selling of all time?",
        answer: "C. Commodore 64",
        options: [
            "A. Apple II",
            "B. IBM PC (5150)",
            "C. Commodore 64",
            "D. Sinclair ZX Spectrum"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "Which company developed the first mobile phone?",
        answer: "A. Motorola",
        options: [
            "A. Motorola",
            "B. Nokia",
            "C. Samsung",
            "D. Apple",
        ]
    },
    {   
        number: 6,
        question: "What year was the oldest programming language still in use invented?",
        answer: "A. 1957",
        options: [
            "A. 1957",
            "B. 1952",
            "C. 1960",
            "D. 1974",
        ]
    },
    {   
        number: 7,
        question: "What was the name of the first operating system?",
        answer: "D. GM-NAA I/O",
        options: [
            "A. Windows 1.01",
            "B. TSS/360",
            "C. EPOC",
            "D. GM-NAA I/O",
        ]
    },
    {   
        number: 8,
        question: "What is the brand Sonos famous for making?",
        answer: "D. Speakers",
        options: [
            "A. Games consoles",
            "B. TV remotes",
            "C. Screens",
            "D. Speakers",
        ]
    },
    {   
        number: 9,
        question: "Where was the world wide web invented?",
        answer: "B. Switzerland",
        options: [
            "A. United States",
            "B. Switzerland",
            "C. Germany",
            "D. United Kingdom",
        ]
    },
    {   
        number: 10,
        question: "Which institution is credited with creating the first website??",
        answer: "C. CERN",
        options: [
            "A. United Nations",
            "B. NASA",
            "C. CERN",
            "D. NATO",
        ]
    }
];

// Export questions variable array to script.js

export default questions;